const sample = [
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Bonjour",
        answer: "Hello",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbddc922aee78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Oui",
        answer: "Yes/No",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3922aee78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Au revoir",
        answer: "Good bye",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3922aee78156bb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Merci",
        answer: "Thank you",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd5822aee78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Pardon",
        answer: "Excuse me",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3922add78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Parlez-vous anglais?",
        answer: "Do you speak English?",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3922aee78176eb94a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "S\u2019il vous plaît",
        answer: "Please",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3226aee78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Je voudrais",
        answer: "I would like",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd3922a2278146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Combien ça coûte?",
        answer: "How much does it cost?",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cb333922aee78146eb90a"
    },
    {
        memoryValue: 1,
        question: "Où sont les toilettes?",
        answer: "Where are the restrooms?",
        __v: 0,
        __id: "5b0cbdd392279e78146eb90a"
    }
]

module.exports = sample;